<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Getting Started with Hugo on Not Applicable Doc</title>
    <link>https://doc.notapplicable.info/getting-started/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Getting Started with Hugo on Not Applicable Doc</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Apr 2020 17:38:14 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://doc.notapplicable.info/getting-started/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Cloning this site and regenerating locally on your own machine</title>
      <link>https://doc.notapplicable.info/getting-started/cloning_this_repository_and_regenerating_the_site_locally/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Nov 2020 13:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://doc.notapplicable.info/getting-started/cloning_this_repository_and_regenerating_the_site_locally/</guid>
      <description>Prerequisites to download the site and push it back to the same or other repositories you need Git.
If you dont already have Git, it can be downloaded from https://git-scm.com/downloads
to rebuild or preiview the site you need hugo in your path. It is a single executable with no installer, just copy the binary somewhere like (for windows) &amp;lsquo;c:\program files&amp;lt;some directory of your choice&amp;gt; and add it to your system path in System Properties - Environment_variables if it is not already or (for Linux / Mac) /usr/local/bin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Installation</title>
      <link>https://doc.notapplicable.info/getting-started/installation/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Apr 2020 17:45:07 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://doc.notapplicable.info/getting-started/installation/</guid>
      <description>The following steps are here to help you initialize your new website. If you don&amp;rsquo;t know Hugo at all, we strongly suggest you learn more about it by following this great documentation for beginners.
Create your project Hugo provides a new command to create a new website.
hugo new site &amp;lt;new_project&amp;gt; Install the theme Install the Hugo-theme-learn theme by following this documentation
This theme&amp;rsquo;s repository is: https://github.com/matcornic/hugo-theme-learn.git
Alternatively, you can download the theme as .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Editing files</title>
      <link>https://doc.notapplicable.info/getting-started/editting_files/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Nov 2020 15:43:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://doc.notapplicable.info/getting-started/editting_files/</guid>
      <description>Adding a new article and editing its contents Images the following markdown will show an image stored in static/images :
![penguins](/images/penguins_scaled.png) </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publishing a Hugo Site to Github Io</title>
      <link>https://doc.notapplicable.info/getting-started/publishing-a-hugo-site-to-github-io/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Apr 2020 17:18:18 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://doc.notapplicable.info/getting-started/publishing-a-hugo-site-to-github-io/</guid>
      <description>Setting up your Github account To publish to github.io for free, you need to have a current public Github account. Mine is already created under the username of marshyon so this is the name I used to publish this site under. A github.io account is available to all Github account users with their username as subdomain to github.io, for example:
https://marshyon.github.io so you will, when activated have access to your content from a similar url but with your username in place of marshyon of course.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
